<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Julio Zambrano</title>
    <link>https://jzambrano-xyz.github.io/Portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Julio Zambrano</description>
    <generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Julio Zambrano {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://jzambrano-xyz.github.io/Portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://jzambrano-xyz.github.io/Portfolio/project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jzambrano-xyz.github.io/Portfolio/project/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://jzambrano-xyz.github.io/Portfolio/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jzambrano-xyz.github.io/Portfolio/publication/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://jzambrano-xyz.github.io/Portfolio/post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jzambrano-xyz.github.io/Portfolio/post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://jzambrano-xyz.github.io/Portfolio/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jzambrano-xyz.github.io/Portfolio/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I take your privacy seriously. To better protect your privacy I provide this privacy policy notice explaining the way your personal information is collected and used.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Collection of Routine Information&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The only information form in this website is for you to send me a contact email if that is your desire. You can always send me a direct email at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jz.xyz@gmail.com&#34;&gt;jz.xyz@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; if you don&amp;rsquo;t wish to use the given form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have included links on this website for your use and reference. I am not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these websites may differ from my own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Security&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The security of your personal information is important to me, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While I strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, I cannot guarantee its absolute security.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Changes To This Privacy Policy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Privacy Policy is effective as of August 25, 2020 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I reserve the right to update or change my Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. If I make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, I will notify you either through the email address you have provided me, or by placing a prominent notice on my website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contact Information&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For any questions or concerns regarding the privacy policy, please send me an email to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jz.xyz@gmail.com&#34;&gt;jz.xyz@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
